So friends, today we are going to talk
about a great health insurance plan
which is going to be ICICI LB's Elevate
Plan.  Now obviously friends, if you
look at this plan, it is
a best seller plan in the health insurance category.  So
what are the things that you
get in it and what are the hidden clauses
that you should check out.  So
please watch this video till the end.  The
video may be long.  Obviously friends,
be it health insurance or life insurance, everything has to be
discussed.  There are a lot of
hidden things.  So if you
watch this video till the end, you will
get a lot of clarity and it will be easier for you to take your decision,
friends.  So friends my
name is Arun and you are watching Finance V
Arun.  Friends, please subscribe to the channel
because you keep getting insurance and mutual
fund related content on it.
So let's talk about this plan,
here you will see written that it is
powered by AI.  Now what does powered by AI
mean?  Now if you look at today's time,
AI has entered everything.
Now what does AI mean?  Now
what kind of AI will be useful in health insurance
?  So when you purchase this plan, the
questions that are asked to you, that is, it is a
simple thing that when you input your data
in health insurance
on ICSC, then it will
give you customized options there.  Like
what does customize option mean?  You will be asked about some of your
health conditions and
on the basis of those health conditions, the optimum thing for you, that is, what could be the
best, where
you need a little more cover, which add-
on you should take, the AI ​​will do it for you.
However, only you
can understand this, you can use AI or take
suggestions from a good financial advisor or health insurance expert or if you want, you
can also consult us for the best
plan for yourself.  Friends, you will
find the number in the description.  You
can contact us by going there and if you want, you can
book this policy through us also.
So let us now start with the
details of this plan.  So
as you can see written here, the
more magical your health covered the better, that is,
the more magical your health cover is, the
better it will be for you.  So
now we are going to see what magical things are there in it.
So let's move ahead.  So if you
first see their brusher, then
obviously if you buy it then
I will provide you the link in the description.
So you can also download this brochure from there.
So here we see a magician
walking with five bubbles in his hand.  So let us see here
what all they have highlighted
in this plan.  Then I will tell you in more detail about the
hidden things
and what you should look for.
So first of all,
if we talk about the benefit of infinite reset,
you get to see the option here.
Now what does reset mean?  It is a
simple matter that if a claim comes and your
sum insured i.e. whatever you had taken gets
exhausted then it will be
reset to infinity.  But
one thing to notice here is that whenever you
look at any browser, do
not just read it.  The small things
like the terms and conditions which are written are
very small things which
we sometimes do not pay attention to.  For example, if
you look here, you can see two stars.
So now
you also need to understand what these two stars mean.
So, I will explain it to you gradually
as you move forward in this plan
and will
also give you information about where you can read all those things
in more detail, friends.
So in the second bubble it is written
Infinite Claim Amount.  Now
what does infinite claim amount mean?  If you
look at it, the unlimited sum insured, if
someone takes a sum insured of Rs 2 crore or Rs 5 crore, then
it obviously
works like an unlimited sum insured.  But
here what infinite claim amount
means for you is that it is an add-on.  Remember this is
not available in this plan.  You will have to take this add
on.  What will happen in this is that
if you ever get a claim due to your choice, then
you can tell the company that
this time brother, I am going to
use the benefit of this add-on.  That means
I want infinite claim on this claim.  That is, it is simple that even
if my
policy is for a low sum insured,
you will still get an infinite claim amount.
Now we will also see how we can get it there.
Then after that, there
is also infinite loyalty bonus here.  Now
what is loyalty bonus is that you are continuously
running your policy and remember
this is also an add on which is named Power Booster.
Which means that
if you are not getting any claim and you are
renewing your policy with the company every year,
then your sum insured will keep increasing
and we will see how much it will increase
and obviously worldwide
cover is also available here.   There
is international medical cover.  But again remember that there is a
star and hash here, so it will be
necessary to read it.  Now we will tell you
what all these things are and obviously here
you also get the option of Infinite Sum Assured.
So these are the things and
because of this, if you see this, this plan has been
called magical.  Now I will
obviously talk in great detail
whether this is really a magical plan or
not and obviously if you
look at its processor then you will see written
Powered by AI.  Now I have already explained the meaning of AI
that the work of AI here
is only that according to the input you give, the
best plan that can be made for you, that is, the
best health insurance plan will be
offered to you here.
So this is powered by AI.
In the times to come, when all the companies will use AI,
you will get to see those things.
Now friends, I will talk to you
why the company says that this plan is revolutionary.
Now what is so special about it?  Obviously,
whatever we understood a while ago, like
we talked about infinite claim amount,
now we will also see its conditions.  Like it is
written in it that get one time infinite
claim amount for your selected claim, that is,
you will decide in which claim
you want to take infinite claim.  For example,
suppose someone has taken a sum insured of ₹ lakh
and he has taken an add-on with
infinite claim amount.  Now when his
claim comes, suppose his claim comes to
around Rs 30-40 lakh.  Now obviously
he has a sum insured of Rs 20 lakh.  So he
can decide there that this time I want to
take the infinite claim amount.
But remember, you will get this only one time
infinite claim amount.  That means,
when you take the policy with the company, then
you will get it only once.  And what is
written here as Star One, which I was telling you is a
hidden condition.  So remember that when
you read this brochure in detail, when you
read its last page, it is
written 'Clear Cut' here.  I will show it to you
and I will also
attach the screenshot here.  It states that
Infinite Care add-on can be opted only
during the first two policy years for
domestic coverage only.  This means that it will
not be available in worldwide coverage.  Will this be
available in domestic coverage and when will it be
available?  When you take the policy, you will not get
this benefit after two years of its starting.
So
remember this thing.  The second option friends
is Infinite Super Loyalty Bonus.
As I already told you,
if you do not have any claim and are
continuing the policy, then
if you take this add-on, then 100%
every year there is irrespective of claim for an
indefinite period with Power Booster.  This
means that even if a claim is made and
if you have taken this add-on Infinite
Super Loyalty Bonus, then your
sum insured will keep increasing by 100% for an indefinite period.  That
means you can use this add-on
if you need it.  Now you should understand how it can be used,
if you suppose you are young, that is,
if you are 28, 30, 35 years old
and you are taking a plan for yourself, you know
that the chances of illness are less now, then you can
also take a low sum insured, that is, obviously the
premium will be less there,
if you take this add-on by taking a low sum insured, then after some time your
sum insured will keep increasing with that loyalty bonus,
so
you can see this benefit here and
in this also start to is applied, that is,
if we see at the second number in it, then it is saying
that power booster, that is, super
loyalty bonus add-on cannot be opted with
unlimited sum insured option.  The bonus can be
utilized only after the annual sum insured is
exhausted.  That is, it is a simple matter that
if you see it,
it will not work on the option of unlimited sum insured
because the simple matter is that
your sum insured there itself is very heavy and
you can use the loyalty bonus only when
your basic sum insured gets exhausted.
So friends, this is also one thing here.
Now if we go further, then after this
if we talk about the third option, it is
Infinite Assurance.  This is also given in it.
Now what does this mean?  Get your
pre existing disease covered from day 31
of the jump started on.  That is, there
is an add-on by giving a jump start in which if you have
any pre-existing disease, then you can get it done on the
31st day.  Generally, if you see, the
waiting period for pre-existing disease is
two to three years.  But here you can
start it from the 31st day itself.
But again look here also, there
is a mark here by doing star three.  It means
something, that is, it is on some selected diseases.
As I am telling you that Jump
Start is applicable only in case of
Asthma, Diabetes, Hypertension,
Hyperlipidemia,
Obesity and Coronary Artery Disease with
ETCA done at least one year prior to the
policy issuance for policy issuance
Applicable for Domestic Coverage only and all
for the period of three continuous
policy years.  That means you can take the jump start add on.  This
means that you can get your pre-
existing diseases covered from the 31st day.
But these diseases are pre-
existing diseases, you
can understand that there is a limit to some of them.  For some diseases,
as I already told you about BP,
diabetes and if you have BP, diabetes
, asthma and one or two diseases which
I just mentioned, then
you can do them.  But remember
when will you get this add on?  When you purchase a continuous three-
year policy here.
After that, if we talk about Infinite Reset,
then you can understand the meaning of Infinite Reset that is,
get refill for your coverage
unlimited times, multiple claims with neither of you now
with the reset benefit, that is,
your sum insured will be covered
unlimited times,
you can take multiple claims, but in this also again
two stars are mentioned here, so now if we talk about two stars, then it is
mentioned here that Reset
Benefit will not trigger in the first claim, that is,
you cannot use it in the first claim.
After the first claim, when the second
claim comes, it will be activated for you.
So this is one thing to understand here and
after that it is mentioned here that the reset
benefit amount cannot be carried forward
for two subsequent years.  This means that the reset
amount will
not be carried forward.  It will end that year.  That is,
your base sum assured.  The next
policy you have will be based on your base sum
insured.  This means that you will have to
purchase it every time.
Option for infinite results.  It is not that once you do it
you think it is infinite.  No worries, it won't be like that
next year.  So this is
something to understand that I have told you.
Now let me go into the proper details of what all
you get in such a health insurance plan.   If
the video looks good as of now,
please like it.  Please subscribe to the channel
friends.  Now if you look into it, the
basic covers of health insurance are
almost the same in every company.
If I talk about the basic cover, then in-
patient treatment means
that if due to any disease or
accident you are hospitalized for
more than 24 hours, then here
you can see that your hospitalization
cover is up to the annual sum insured.  But
remember there is room rent capping here.   There is a
capping on room rent here.
Here you will get only single private
AC room.  Now you will think that this is a best
seller plan.  But I am
getting a single private AC room here.  Brother, how can this happen
?  So you can understand that
if I give you an overall idea in this plan,
then
you are also getting worldwide coverage in it.
You will also get maternity benefits here.  So when such a
plan is made then its premium
becomes very high.  So, somewhere or the other, an
adjustment will be made to cut the premium.  Now many
people might be thinking that I do
n't need a cabin in the room rent, so there
is an add-on for that, but
if you take that add-on then you will definitely get the
option of a single private AC room here
and obviously my advice
to people is that generally you should
look for such a plan or take such an add-on in
which the capping of room rent is removed
because when there is hospitalization in a hospital due to
any emergency, then you do not
think that I only need a single private AC
room.  It is possible that at that time there was
no single private AC room and there were
some upper level rooms, that is, if there were very expensive rooms,
then their cost is
not just the cost of the room, the
doctor's fees also increase in it, the cost of everything increases, so
if
you are thinking of purchasing this plan, then at
least take one add-on
which should be the room modifier,
about which I will definitely talk to you a
little later, so in-patient
treatment is covered here, after that if we
talk about day care procedure treatment, it
means that nowadays,
due to medical advancement, such processes have started happening
that it is not necessary that for some things
you have to be admitted in the hospital for 24 hours.
For example, suppose someone has an
accident and breaks his arm or leg, then
what is generally happening these days?  You went to the hospital, got an
X-ray done, after that the doctor applied plaster
etc., gave you medicine and sent you home, and
you came back home in two-four hours, so it is not that if
you were not hospitalized then
you will not get the claim.  So, if something happens to you
due to the day care procedures,
you will get a claim up to the annual sum insured.
After that, if we
talk about donor expenses, donor means
if you are going to have an organ transplant, then the hospitalization expenses of the person who is
donating the organ to you or
if you call him organ harvester, then the
hospitalization expenses of
your donor will also be
covered in organ harvesting up to the annual sum insured. Talking about pre and post
hospitalization medical expenses, then
pre hospitalization is of 90 days
and post hospitalization is of 180 days.  This means
that whenever you get any illness,
you do not directly go and get admitted.
Sometimes you will consult your family doctor,
then take medicine from him, then get a
diagnosis done, only then you will come to know
that there is no major problem.  So you will get the
expenses incurred for your admission till 90 days ago and after getting cured of the disease and getting
discharged, then for the
quantity of days, whatever you want, be it
medicines or tests,
you will get the expenses of that too here through claim friends.
After that, if we talk about domiciliary
hospitalization, then sometimes there are such conditions
that hospitalization is not possible
in the hospital, so if the doctor gives in writing
that your treatment will be done at
home, then you will
get the benefit of domiciliary hospitalization here,
but remember that the advice should be
from a medical practitioner i.e. a reputed doctor and at least it should be for
more than three days continuously, only then
you will get this claim.  After that, if we
talk about insurance IS hospitalization,
then IS treatment is covered in it,
reimbursement up to annual sum insured and in cases where
whatever is possible will be done for you,
domestic road ambulance is covered here,
road ambulance expenses for
transferring the insured to the nearest
hospital, whichever hospital is near you, for
accident, illness, for emergency care due to any reason, then
your road ambulance
cover up to annual sum insured is also available in the base plan of this plan, that is,
this is not an add-on, this
means that if you buy this plan, then
you will basically get all these things there.
Apart from this, see here
some different benefits have been given to you.
Surrogacy and Oocyte.  Now this means that
you know about surrogacy, that is, when someone
like you is unable to become a parent,
then what do they do?  You can have
your test tube baby through surrogacy, that is,
through the donor, that is, the surrogate mother, then
you will get the money for it up to a maximum of Rs 5 lakh,
even in the case of surrogacy or oocyte.  So
now friends, if we talk about reset benefit,
then here you can see that
your reset will be 100%,
whatever your annual sum insured is, it will
remain up to 100% and this will continue for unlimited times, be it
any disease, illness,
injury, but remember that the
double stars in it mean
that it will not be activated in the first claim,
it will be activated only after the next claim in the year,
friends, varicose surgery,
varicose surgery means if you have started having any such disease due to your BMI, that is,
generally speaking, due to obesity.
Then the doctor says that it is necessary for you to reduce your weight
and for that surgery is done,
so there its
hospitalization for obesity, you
can see that even the annual sum insured
is covered here.  Loyalty Bonus means continuous
renewal with the company, then your
community bonus will increase by 20% up to maximum 100%
of annual sum insured.  That means,
suppose someone has taken a cover of Rs 20 lakh.
Now if no claim comes, then
what is 20% of 20 lakhs next year?  ₹4 lakh more will be
added to it.  So
you will get these things in terms of loyalty bonus.  Wellness
programs also continue.  And you
can understand that if you join the wellness program directly, that is,
if you join their wellness program
which is through the app,
then you will get some discount at the time of renewal.  If
you
join Wellness and stay fit,
you will obviously be given a discount because of it.
Discount on services and products.
Now what can I say about this, they have an app
where you will get discounts etc.
I
consider it necessary to discuss this for consultation with doctors etc. on some services.  You should understand that
you will get the option of Health Assistant here, that is, there will be
some
experts there, if you feel something
related to your health, then you can
clear your doubts there and will be
given the option of Technology and Advancement, Advancement and Treatment.
Due to technological advancement,
you can see that whatever claim you receive,
you will get the claim up to the annual sum insured,
friends.  So these were the overall basic covers
here.  If you like the video so far, please
like it and subscribe to the channel.
I know video is going big.
But brother, I have to talk in detail.
So now you think whether I am saying anything nonsense.
So because of this the videos become
bigger.  So friends, now if we talk about
this plan, if you look at things overall, then it is
mostly a game of add-ons
because there are a lot of add-ons available here.
As you will see here,
you will get the option of worldwide cover.  So
you can get worldwide treatment worth up to Rs 3 crore here.  If we
talk about cashless, that too worldwide, then USA
is also included here.  But here the waiting period is
two years, which you can reduce to one
year.  If you
pay additional premium then you get this option here.  The
option of two-hour hospitalization is also given here.  That is,
sometimes what happens is that you get hospitalized even within two hours.
Which may include room rent
[sound of clearing throat],
practitioner's fees, ICU charges
also.  So you can also take this add on.
Now if you look here, it has
brought you an option with percentage.   It becomes
important for you to understand these hidden terms.  So it means covers
the medical expenses for the hospitalization
of the insured person for a minimum of two
hours during the policy period.  If we talk about AYUSH
treatment, that is,
for those who want to undergo AYUSH treatment, then
24-hour hospitalization is necessary.
Otherwise, if you
look at modern treatment, the hospitalization is more than two hours
and if you take this add-on, then
you will get the claim here.  There is
no problem in this.
NRI Advantage: Now see for whom it
is important, you can understand.
If people living outside want, they can take this as an
add-on.  So when you
come to India, it is a simple thing that
you can get the treatment done there and
you will also get a discount
of 25% on renewal at 20%.  So right now it is
not that important for everyone.  Chronic Disease
Management Program Now this
is a management program.  Remember,
you can understand that chronic disease means asthma.
Diabetes, hypertension, high cholesterol,
obesity and if you talk about such
diseases, now if you take this add-on then
their management programs
will run and you can avail their benefits through them.
So you will get some peace of mind.  There
is an option of infinite care.  Now
as I have already mentioned that one
time infinite claim we have already discussed.
So we will not discuss it now.
Compensated visit means that if your
hospitalization is more than 5 days
then your ₹0000 will be refunded to you. Now it
is a simple matter, what is the meaning of compensation?  If you
are admitted then someone or the other would be coming to meet you,
family members, so you can understand
that they will give up to ₹00 in one policy year.
Whether you travel by economy class air
or by train, your
travel expenses up to ₹0000 will be compensated.
After that there is also Senior Care Value Added Service,
which you can understand, for people above 55 years of age,
some things are necessary for them,
as you can see,
physiotherapy sessions etc. have been done, then if you
take this add-on now, you will get its benefit here,
after that if we talk about
some power boosters, super loyalty bonus,
I have already discussed this in the beginning, so we will
not talk about it,
you can understand for whom domestic air ambulance cover is necessary, if
you want to take it, then take it, this is also
an add-on, so it will cover the air ambulance,
whatever is yours till the sum insured, and but
remember, it is not like that if you go
travelling anywhere, you will get
domestic air ambulance
cover here for the policy period, whichever is the nearest hospital from here.  We have already talked about jump start
in the beginning.
So now we will not talk about it because it is taking
too much time.  Then there is
dependent accommodation benefit, that is, if
suppose you are the earning member in the house and
you have a dependent, that is, you can also have children.  It could
also be your dependent or wife.
So obviously your income has been
affected, so if you take this add-on in this policy,
then you will get accommodation for your dependents up to ₹1000 per day.
Up to ₹1000.  Remember, 1000 is not for everyone.
It depends on your sum
insured.  The bigger it is, the maximum amount
you will get there will be ₹1000 only.
But the condition is that your
minimum hospitalization should be for three days
and at the most they will
pay for only 10 days.  That means if the
hospitalization is for more than 10 days, it will not be
given.  So,
you will get this dependent accommodation
benefit for any stay between three to 10 days.  Talking about claim protector,
now you know that
in health insurance, you do not get claim for things like cotton
, gloves, syringes, injections
, masks etc.
So if you take this add-on then
you will start getting claims for all these things too, friends.  That
means that claim
protector itself is a good add on.  You
can consider this.  So now friends, if we
talk about the New One Baby Cover, then as soon as the
child is born, his cover will start.  Will last
for 90 days.  Whatever your
maternity is, whoever will monitor your maternity coverage.
This
newborn baby cover will last till her twilight.  Then if we talk about
inflation protector, here
you can see that every year you see
inflation is increasing, so if you choose sum insured
of 10 lakhs today, then next year
[sound of clearing throat] it will not be 10 lakhs
in real value, so if you
take this add on, then your
sum insured will be increased accordingly, friends.
Talking about nursing at home,
if you see this rebate, if you require nursing at home,
nursing etc., then up
to ₹000 will be given for that, for a maximum of 10
days, for post hospitalization, that is, when you
go home after being discharged from the hospital, then it will be given at that time,
but that qualified nurse should be at
your home.  So these will do the ribs here.
If you take this add on.  Then if we
talk about maternity benefit, this is also an
add-on.  You don't get this in the base plan.
So what you can do here is
that whatever maternity benefit you take, it will be 10%
of the annual sum insured and maximum up to Rs 1 lakh.  That
means, you should understand that even if you
take a plan of Rs 10 lakh, then 10% of Rs 10 lakh
becomes Rs 1 lakh.  So if you
choose a sum insured of Rs 10 lakh and then
take the add-on maternity benefit, then he will get a
maximum sum insured of Rs 1 lakh.
But remember, there is a waiting
period of two years.  It is not like that, it has been there since the
beginning.  After that, durable
medical equipment cover, that is, some such
equipment is installed sometimes
after some accident.  So if you
take this add-on there, then
you will get medical cover for equipment worth up to Rs 5 lakh,
friends.  So this is an add on.  Now
after that let's talk about some more add ons.  There are so many that you can decide
which one is useful to you and which one is
not.  You should see this.  Vaccination
for new born baby covered in the first year.
If we talk about the vaccinations that a child needs in the first year, then
if you
take EA on, your 1% of sum assured will be up
to a maximum of Rs 10,000.  So you
see how important this is.  Conveyance
Benefit means that if you are
admitted for 10 days or more, then
due to any accident or illness, then this one time benefit will be
given to you at ₹00 in the policy year so that whatever
your expenses etc. may be, that
extra benefit is being given to you here.
You can also avail health checkup add-on.
You will not get a checkup every year here.  You will
take this as an add-on only but
you can see that you will get it for a maximum of ₹000.
Here it is 0.5% of annual
sum insured and this is on cashless basis, that is,
you can go to their labs and get it done.  Ca
n't get it done anywhere else.
Now these things are options to reduce
maternity benefits.  You can get this done.
If you want to avail maternity benefit
and want to reduce the waiting period from two years to one
year, then you can do this.
This will be done at an extra premium.
After that there is the option of V Fit here.  That means
you can understand that through their app you will be able to
see OPD i.e. doctors.
Pharmacy will be visible.  So you
can order medicine and diagnostic from there.  So
you will get some discounts there.  So here
you see how important it is.  One
can understand that personal accident is a proper
insurance in which what will happen is that if
you take it, suppose someone has taken it for Rs 50 lakh for a
personal accident and
suppose he dies, then
Rs 1 lakh will be given to his nominee.  Do you understand
?  And this maximum age will be up to 65 years.
It is not available after that.
Tele consultation is again an add on brother.
In this, if you want, brother,
you
can talk to good teleconsultant medical practitioners through audio-video online
portal, if you can understand, but
how useful it is depends on you,
you should understand it and see it.
You can also take add-on for critical illness here,
which are 20 listed critical
illnesses, here you can get extra up to Rs 50 lakh,
if you see here, you can
take insurance for critical illness
and you will get this only if you are between 18 to 50 years of age.
Now what I was talking about room rent, you
can see it here.   There
is an option of room modifier, like
in the base plan you get a single private AC room,
here you can upgrade it
or downgrade it.  If you
downgrade, the premium will definitely reduce
but this is the most useless thing.  You can
take this room modifier and upgrade it.
Remove the capping on room rent.  Only then will
things be better.  Voluntary
Comment: If you choose the comment option
of 10, 20, 30, 40, 50% then the premium will
definitely reduce.  But again this is useless.
For example, if you choose even 10%, then
you will have to pay 10% of whatever claim comes.  The
company will pay the rest.  So what is the
benefit of this?  What will you get by reducing it by two to four thousand rupees
?  So this is the thing.  Now
talking about its information, here you
can see that you can take this for your entry age from 18 years
to 125 years.  That means there is
no maximum age limit.  Is it on some
things that I have already discussed?  Even if you have
children above 18 years of age, you can add them
in the individual policy or the family policy.
Sum options ranging from Rs 5 lakh to Rs 3 crore
are available for you.  If
I talk about the tenure option, then options ranging from one to five years
are available for you.  That means
you can buy a continuous policy for one year only
, if you have bought it for two years, four years or five years,
that is an option for you.  You
can check the family floater limit here.
Here you can include two adults and three children
in the family floater policy.
Child considered dependent till 30 years.   This
means that whatever children you have will be
counted as your dependents for 30 years.
So this is the thing, that is, you
can consider it if you want.  There
is no need to buy them separately.
After that, if we talk about waiting periods,
you can see here that there are some waiting
periods.  The initial waiting period
in every insurance is 30 years.  That
is, the pre-existing waiting period is 36 months
which you can reduce.  The
waiting period for specific diseases from the add-ons that I told you about is 24 months i.e.
two years.  The critical illness waiting
period is 90 days if you take the add-on.
Bariatric surgery means the
disease which occurs due to obesity or EMI.  If he is undergoing surgery then he is
two years old.  The waiting period for
diabetes, HTN, cardiac conditions, i.e.
heart-related conditions, if it is
not a pre-existing disease, is 90
days.  The maternity waiting period is 24
months, which can again be reduced
to one year through add-ons,
and the worldwide cover waiting period is again
two years.  So this is some information
and waiting period for you.  So tell me how
you liked it?  If you have any doubt, you will
find the number in the description.  If you
want to purchase a policy then
contact us and if you have any query then
you can also ask in the comments.   If you like the
video then please like it.  Please
subscribe to the channel.  The video has definitely become long
but I hope I have been able to
cover everything here friends.  So
now I will meet you in the next video.  Take
care of yourself till then.  Thank you so much.